Bc. Juraj Gábriel

Košice, 040 17, Slovakia +420 605 941 313 gabriel.juraj@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am strongly interested into the IT sector at the moment and have always had a keen interest in technology, but only recently made it possible to focus on improving my IT skills full time and dedicate myself to be part of the IT world. My past working experience were focused mainly to management and automotive sector.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Branch - Fleet Manager, Auto-Gabriel, Kosice, Slovakia — 2017-2018

- Local AVIS car rental branch with 3 employees and fleet of 50 vehicles.
- Planning, Reporting, Customer and Business contact and Billing.

Dealer Technik, AZ-servis, Brno, Czech Republic — 2014-2015

- Whole process of dealing with customer at Skoda servis.
- Time-Management, Customer care.

EDUCATION

Newton College, Brno, Czech Republic — Global Business and Management, Bachelor degree, 2013-2017

Newton College, Brno, Czech republic — Human Resource Management, Master degree, 2017-present

SKILLS

IT — while working on improving those skills I got experience in Python, Django and some basic knowledge of HTML.

Linguistics — can speak a little Spanish and confidently in Slovak, English and Czech.